

CONTACT

1 (226) 980-9134

Phone Number

Website

gsing994@gmail.com

www.GurmanSingh.com

# Gurman Singh

## **Product Manager**

**SUMMARY** 

An accomplished product management professional with over four years of bringing products to market. Experienced in strategy and leading large product releases to drive over 300 million downloads and 250 million monthly impressions. Highly organized, detail-oriented, and conscientious self-starter, able to strategize and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks with creativity, enthusiasm and humor.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science (Hons) Concentration: Genetic Engineering

The University of Western Ontario

**SKILLS** 

PROCESS MANAGEMENT

SaaS & IaaS BASIC ARCHITECTURE

MARKETING STRATEGY

DIGITAL ADVERTISING

MOBILE MARKETING

WEBSITE DESIGN/HTML



#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



## Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) - Product Manager

May 2018 - Present

- Defined and drove Radeon Software performance plan for new products
- Identified and prioritized software features required to meet new product performance goals
- Prepared regular performance updates for executive teams
- Managed and coordinated specialized performance data for new application releases
- Acquired technical knowledge to work with engineering and execution teams
- Continuously drove the coordination of ISV engineering, performance engineering, driver development teams and technical marketing lab



#### Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) - Product Marketing Specialist

July 2016 - May 2018

- Lead five product and software launches gathering over 1 billion total impressions
- Communicated AMD's value proposition and competitive positioning
- Developed technical and highlevel storytelling for Radeon products
- Conducted campaign analyses to develop company-wide KPIs which anticipate industry trends and provide recommendations for product features
- Created marketing content for sales enablement, marketing newsletters and other customer viewable web content



### The University of Western Ontario - Microsoft Account Specialist

Jan 2015 - May 2016

- Built long term partnerships with customers to enable continued value of Microsoft products
- Drove the adoption of Microsoft platform services through various channel driven activations
- Recognized as a product expert and educated customers on various Microsoft solutions
- Provided products which promoted the integration of accessibility with technology
- Ensured customer value through defining and achieving business outcomes